Wait, it's already noon?
At least my fever's down...
Really? That's a relief.
W-Why?!
Oh, sorry, I've been here all night.
Your fever was running really high.
N-Now that you mention it..
Sorry, it won't take long.
You really do hate the hospital, don't you?
What a revolting development.
I'll never get over it.
Sorry for the trouble I caused you.
Why am I sleeping over here, anyway?
Was I tossing and turning?
I moved you. This is the spot in the
room that's got the best visibility.
If someone comes in, it's gonna be either from the
sliding screen over there or the one next to me,
or maybe the roof, as a long shot, but from
this position, I can protect you regardless.
Who exactly is coming in?
People who want to kill me.
What the hell?
Well, I love you, Yoshino.
So the best way to hurt me
would probably be to kill you.
I don't really get what you mean...
But did you seriously nurse me all
night long, without sleeping?
It's not a big deal.
I can't sleep around
other people anyway.
There's no shortage of people
who have beef with me.
Well, I'm gonna head back to my room.
I let the school know you'd
be taking today off too.
Okay, got it. Thanks.
Wait, hang on a sec.
I'm gonna jump in the bath and then
make some udon. Do you want some?
You probably haven't been eating
well because of me, have you?
Thanks, but I'm good.
Besides, I was thinking
about getting some sleep.
You can just sleep in here, then.
Remember what I said? I have
trouble sleeping around people.
It's fine. If anyone comes
in, I'll kill them for you.
Okay, but what if your love for me
drives you to strangle me in my sleep?
I don't feel even a speck of love for you,
so I'm not gonna kill you just yet.
I see! I guess I'm not worth killing yet.
You never fail to impress,
Yoshino. I love it.
It's settled, then.
Since you're here, you may
as well hit the bath, too.
Hang on.
That's... I'm not sure.
Sure about what?
I mean, I think it'd be good. Great, even.
But... How do I put this?
It feels a bit like when you drop by
a relative's house for the Bon holiday
and end up spending the night?
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you gonna bathe or not?
Uh... I will.
Make sure to get some protein, too.
You're still growing.
There's plenty more, too.
They sent a bunch from Osaka.
Thanks for the food.
Princess
Tsubaki
I finally made it back to school...
Math II+B:
Calculations
<Solutions Guide>
What do I do?
I am seriously screwed for finals.
It'll be fine. You've got two more days.
Two days ain't gonna be enough!
Plus, I've got math on day one.
I can tutor you, then.
What? No. You've got your
own studying to do.
I never spend too much
time studying for exams.
I just do the work and then
review my notes and the text.
How do you study the rest of the time, then?
I tend to read all the
textbooks during class.
Then, once I solve the mock
questions, that's a wrap.
I shoulda known better than to ask...
Can I even get into college if I'm
tripping over basic math?
It'll work out.
Even if it doesn't, if you ever need some
math done, I can handle it for you.
You're saying that like it's
a given we get married.
Oh, speaking of college.
Once the last day of exams is over,
I'm heading to Yokohama.
Yokohama?
My cousin's moving from Kyoto to Yokohama.
Well, are you ready?
You didn't need to come with.
It'd be dangerous to leave
two girls on their own.
Besides, I know my way around here.
I guess that makes sense. You come here often?
Not on my own, no.
Well, in terms of going all the
way to Yokohama from Tokyo...
In most cases, it'd be
for a date, wouldn't it?
Not much of a liar, are you?
I just thought that trying to make excuses
at this point would make you even angrier.
Hey, you're learning!
It's 1PM.
My cousin might be a bit late,
she's busy with the move.
She's a year older than you, right?
So she'll be in college
when fall comes around.
Yeah. How much
do you know about her anyway?
A fair amount.
What's fair?
Your father and her mother
were half-siblings.
Sure as hell sounds like
you did your homework!
Technically, she's the daughter of the
daughter of one of Grandpa's mistresses...
Mistress
Renji
Wife
Yoshino's
Father
Cousin's
Mother
Half-Siblings
Sounds like a complicated family.
That's the yakuza for you.
The thing is, this mistress suddenly
turned back up when my aunt was ten,
so there's a bit of ambiguity as to
whether or not there's a blood relation.
Say hello to your daughter.
But Grandpa didn't ask any questions
and went on to raise her, which
makes her my aunt either way.
Your cousin's been attending
an international school
since she was young and has
studied overseas by herself.
And when she starts college this fall,
she'll be doing international studies...
Sounds like a pretty typical rich girl.
Ugh, now that I think about it,
she's exactly your type!
What do you mean?
Yoshino-chan!
It's been so long! How've you been?
Did you lose some weight?
Does it look that way? I don't think I did.
Lucky for me, I've been fine!
I have to say, Yoshino-chan...
You still look just like Renji-san!
It's a relief that you're adorable as ever.
I still have no idea what you mean by that.
Is this gentleman the one I've heard about?
Hello, it's nice to meet you.
I'm Miyama Kirishima.
It's a pleasure. I'm Akashigata Tsubaki.
See what I mean?
Exactly his type
She's a thoroughbred princess
with the fashion sense to match!
Pale skin, dark eyes, with
a long, black hime cut!
There aren't a lot of girls who
can pull off this look!
No matter how you slice it, she's one of them
"girls that other girls hate" that you love!
That's rich, coming from you, Yoshino-chan.
Come on Yoshino, even you
shouldn't be that rude.
She really is pretty, though.
I can see how she's your cousin.
It's an honor to meet such a beauty.
See? Just like I told you.
A real smooth talker.
I'd heard Yoshino-chan's boyfriend was a
looker, and it seems the rumors are true.
Thank you.
Hey, he's not my boyfriend!
By the way, Yoshino-chan, how'd
your end-of-term tests go?
You really wanna ask, huh?
Oh, that makes it pretty obvious.
You don't need to worry.
We stayed up late studying.
Nah, I'm still worried. My math
answers were a total mess.
Forget college, what am I gonna
do if I can't even graduate?
Maybe we could open a flower
shop if it comes to that.
What kinda half-assed comfort is that?
Actually, you're from Kyoto,
right Tsubaki-san?
Right.
I get to hear Yoshino's accent occasionally,
but not in a conversation with
someone else who has one.
Well, Kyoto and Osaka accents
have their differences,
but they probably sound similar to you.
True enough. Both my grandmother
and mother are from Kyoto.
I'm shocked you actually decided to move.
I had you pegged for living in
Kyoto until the day you died.
It's a stereotype for Kyoto
girls to love Kyoto so much
that they refuse to marry out
of the city, ending up alone,
and Tsubaki is a real model Kyotoite.
Since we're out here, Yoshino-chan,
we had better check the stores.
I don't really want anything, though...
How 'bout you?
I could go for a new tote
bag to take to school.
Oh, Yoshino, what about these san—
Yoshino, how about these sandals?
You mentioned you wanted new ones,
right? I bet they'd look great on you.
Hey, look at that! They're so cute.
Turn this way real quick.
Y'know, I'm pretty sure they'd give me a ten
centimeter lift, so I'd be this tall with 'em on.
I don't mind.
Well, I do!
Doesn't whether or not they
look good on you matter more?
Chinatown
I ate too much...
Are you okay, Yoshino?
The last time I got carried away and ate
dim sum, it really did me in.
Meat Buns
Shark Fin Ramen
Dim Sum
You always do this, Yoshino-chan.
I remember last time, it was
at the Chinatown in Kobe.
You're every bit as beautiful as Renji-san.
I bet you'd be cuter with a little fluff!
Yeah, yeah. Renji-san, Renji-san.
I take it by Renji-san you mean Boss Somei?
Tsubaki thinks the old coot's
perfect for some reason.
Bwahahahaha
I love
everything
about him
Incorrect! While he does
have his imperfections,
those are what makes him so uniquely
charming, which is wonderful!
Not only that but his looks, his face,
and his build are all essentially flawless!
Renji-san is a masterpiece
crafted by the gods!
Is somethin' wrong with your brain?
Boss Somei is definitely handsome, though.
And Yoshino takes after
him by being so pretty.
Doesn't she?
I hate to disagree with you, Tsubaki-san,
but Yoshino is the perfect
one as far as I'm concerned.
Why are you getting competitive?
You know, Yoshino, you have to be careful
with smooth talkers. They tend to cheat.
Yeah, he's got a whole roster
of chicks on the side.
Besides, you're one to talk!
Oh, no. I've been so busy lately that I
don't have enough time for that many.
Liar. How many have you
got lined up right now?
Three...
Timing?
I'm flexible on who's the main boy, so I
don't count whoever that is, though.
That's way too flexible!
She's like you. She's got no restraint
when it comes to this stuff.
I can see how most guys would be hard
pressed to say no to such a beauty.
Why, thank you.
How far have you two gotten? Any sex yet?
What the hell is wrong you?!
No, I imagine if we had
any premarital intimacy,
I'd be killed twice over by
both her and her family.
Besides, delayed satisfaction
is always sweeter,
so I'm pretty pleased
with the way things are.
Is that how you see this situation?!
Really? I'd always thought that,
in the name of sisterhood,
that I'd want to make love to
the first man to have Yoshino.
No objections from me, there.
How about you two screw each
other and leave me out of it?!
Dammit, just being around you is exhausting!
It's giving me crazy cravings for sweets!
Oh, you just said you were full.
But get a load of that shaved ice...
True, it does look good.
I'm not sure I can handle
a full serving though...
Then—
Then why don't I order one?
If you can't finish it, I will.
For real? Seriously?
Yeah. I'll go order it now.
Nah, since I'm gonna be the one eating it,
I wanna wash my hands, too.
It's a relief to see
Yoshino-chan doing so well.
So much has happened, I had been worried.
True enough. As tough as she is, she
does tend to take unnecessary risks.
I'll make sure to cover for her.
I'm not worried about that part.
You seem pretty considerate,
when you want to be.
And more predictable than I thought.
Well, that's a first.
Yoshino always calls me
an unpredictable scumbag.
She's right about that.
That's a little harsh.
I'm sure I'd feel the same
way if she weren't around,
but the way you treat us differently really
paints the whole picture, doesn't it?
What do you mean?
You don't enjoy talking with me at all.
You don't really want to
talk in the first place,
and have nothing to say, so you just
spout whatever I want to hear.
Which is probably why most girls
are on an emotional roller coaster
from whatever nonsense you feel
like saying in the moment.
That's the first time I've heard that, too.
What really surprises me is the way
you anticipate what Yoshino wants
and capitalize on it before anyone else does.
It's not just that, either. Whenever
Yoshino brings something up,
you pay much closer attention.
You want to be kind to her. And you
want her affection, if you can get it.
Though it seems like that's
not the case, so far.
I wasn't sure about asking this, but...
Let's hear it.
When Yoshino—
I bought it!
Get a load of the mangoes!
Huh? Did I interrupt something?
Nah, just a bit of idle chitchat.
Oh, that looks yummy!
Right? You can have some, Tsubaki.
Huh? I wonder who's calling.
It's Inamori-san.
Hello?
Yeah? Yeah.
From the school?
No, I understand. Thank
you for letting me know.
Right, I'll be back as soon as possible.
What's up?
The school called...
Apparently a few of the sheets from
my math homework were missing.
I forgot that I had them
stuck in my textbook.
What did the teacher say?
They're willing to wait until 8PM.
We need to get back ASAP, then.
By taxi is probably fastest.
Yoshino, I'm gonna drop Tsubaki-san
off at her hotel before heading back.
Oh, okay. Take care of her for me.
Of course.
Alright, I guess we should get going.
I guess so.
But how about a little date first?
I was expecting that.
Where should we go?
Let me think...
It's been a long time since
I was on a Ferris wheel.
Likewise. I'll have to make
sure Yoshino doesn't find out.
Tsubaki-san, you know about
the Doseikai Group, right?
They're the country's largest
civilian medical group.
Right.
The man your mother has been
seeing for the past 15 years
is the director of a Kyoto
Doseikai hospital, right?
Oh, you know about Papa, too?
There's a lot of nasty
rumors about the Doseikai.
An Empire of Medicine:
Doseikai money linked with—
From political donations to working with
the mob, and maybe, most notably...
illegal organ transplants.
And?
I'll be blunt: Where is
Yoshino's kidney right now?
Selling a kidney isn't the kind
of thing just anybody can do.
I had thought about selling my own organs,
but it's hard to do in Japan
without the right connections.
Oh, what made you want to do that?
Well, I was the reason Yoshino sold one of
hers, so I figured I'd sell one of mine, too.
If only you had asked me.
I'm pretty sure you're the only person
she could've turned to about this.
But, despite all my searching,
I couldn't find Yoshino's kidney...
Which made me realize maybe you hadn't
sold her kidney in the first place.
Why, whatever do you mean?
That you didn't take it
out in the first place.
And you just handed her the four million yen.
I was able to get a good look
when she was sick in bed,
and she had a small scar above
her waist on the left side.
Not what you'd expect in terms of size
or location from that kind of procedure.
Which leaves me with two options for
confirming whether or not it was taken out:
I either have Yoshino get an
MRI or I ask you about it.
I wonder if anyone's ever had this kind
of conversation on a Ferris wheel before.
What's your big interest in Yoshino-chan?
Do you remember the first expensive
thing you ever bought, Tsubaki-san?
Mine was a ticket for the Shinkansen.
It was July 22nd of my third
year of middle school,
I scraped together the little money I had to
get a seat on the 12PM to Shin-Osaka station.
Because I had heard there was going
to be a Kirigaya-gumi funeral,
and that Boss Somei's granddaughter
would be attending.
Does she know about that?
No.
And when you ask why I'm so interested in
her, I can only say it's because I'm in love.
I don't remember the first
expensive thing I bought,
but I can tell you about
something I got recently.
One and a half liters
of blood for four million yen.
I drained her of as much blood as I safely
could without touching her kidneys.
And she doesn't know this,
but I held onto the blood.
Would you want it?
Oh, of course. You can name your price.
Too bad!
This is no good. Not only did I trick her,
now I'm blabbing about it, too.
Plus, I can't have you go telling her.
Why take the blood?
That's a pretty serious amount.
There could've been side effects.
And what would you have
done if she had died?
I tried to talk her out of it, but...
I'd rather die than let
him make a fool outta me.
She insisted.
It wouldn't exactly be worth the trouble
unless she gambled her life, no?
I appreciate you humoring me.
You're actually as charming as Yoshino is.
I guess it's because you're cousins?
You really are a smooth-talking lowlife.
Well, Yoshino-chan seems to be doing
well, so I'll leave it at that.
But if you end up being a
totally worthless scumbag,
you should watch out.
Even if it takes plastic surgery,
I'll make sure you spend your whole
life looking for her and never find her.
I'll keep that in mind.
But what's the criteria for being
a worthless scumbag, exactly?
Why, it's completely at my discretion.
Man, I'm glad I made it in time!
You won't have to worry about
your assignments, at least.
The exams are still freaking me out,
but the idea of not getting credit for the
assignments had me in a real death spiral.
Feelin' a bit better now!
Were you able to ask Tsubaki
about what you wanted to know?
What are you talking about?
You don't have to pretend.
I knew you'd dig around.
I guess so...
What? I'm not gonna ask
what you talked about.
I don't really care.
You don't?
I might not trust you, but
I definitely trust her.
Besides, if the two of you started to work
together against me, I wouldn't mind.
I'm the one who chose to trust her.
So if she got the drop on
me, then that's on me.
You two really are alike.
We are? I don't think anyone's
ever said that before.
Speak of the devil, it's from her.
You and her traded contact info?!
Yep. To hang out some other time.
Well, you really hit it off...
She settled on an apartment.
Really? Tell her to send the address,
and I'll get her a housewarming present.
Here's the picture of Yoshino-chan
I promised you.
What the hell?! Delete it! Delete it, fast!
So cute...
You're gonna blackmail me by threatening
to post it online, ain't you?!
Not on my life! That'd be such a waste!
Please, just let me keep it! It's fine!
Hell no!
Renji-san in his teens... amazing!
Much obliged, Kirishima-san.